<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Module 2: Designing Scalable, Cost Optimized Solutions on AWS Turkey Builders Day</title>
    <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lab Module 2: Designing Scalable, Cost Optimized Solutions on AWS Turkey Builders Day</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:52:43 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing and Deploying Applications</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/ci-cd-eb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:58:18 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/ci-cd-eb/</guid>
      <description>Objectives In this lab you will quickly develop, build, and deploy an applications on AWS.
Services Used in this Lab:  AWS CodeStar enables you to quickly develop, build, and deploy applications on AWS. AWS CodeStar provides a unified user interface, enabling you to easily manage your software development activities in one place.
 With AWS CodeStar, you can set up your entire continuous delivery toolchain in minutes, allowing you to start releasing code faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying a Scalable Web Application to Production</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/asg-lb-eb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:58:18 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/asg-lb-eb/</guid>
      <description>Objectives In this lab you will quickly replicate your development environment you created in the previous lab and deploy to production with scalability enabled.
Services Used in this Lab:  AWS Elastic Beanstalk is an easy-to-use service for deploying and scaling web applications and services developed with Java, .NET, PHP, Node.js, Python, Ruby, Go, and Docker on familiar servers such as Apache, Nginx, Passenger, and IIS.
 Upload your code and Elastic Beanstalk automatically handles the deployment, from capacity provisioning, load balancing, auto-scaling to application health monitoring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cost Explorer for understanding and managing costs</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/costmon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 17:58:18 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/lab-wa/costmon/</guid>
      <description>Objectives In this lab you will quickly develop, build, and deploy an applications on AWS.
Services Used in this Lab:  AWS Cost Explorer has an easy-to-use interface that lets you visualize, understand, and manage your AWS costs and usage over time. Get started quickly by creating custom reports (including charts and tabular data) that analyze cost and usage data, both at a high level (e.g., total costs and usage across all accounts) and for highly-specific requests (e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>