<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on AWS Turkey Builders Day</title>
    <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on AWS Turkey Builders Day</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:33:15 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/prerequisites/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:39:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/prerequisites/</guid>
      <description>Preparing Cloud Environment Your first lab will focus on preparing your cloud environment and will take around 10 minutes. You need to complete this first lab, otherwise it might be harder for you to complete the following labs.
Services that you will be using in this lab:
AWS Account  AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) - AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) enables you to manage access to AWS services and resources securely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expected Costs</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:44:22 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/costs/</guid>
      <description>Understanding Free Tier Watch this 3 minute Knowledge center video from AWS: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rkKvzCskpLE
Expected Costs You are responsible for the cost of the AWS services used while running this lab. As of the date of publication, the baseline cost for running this solution as-is should be around 2-5 USD depending if you are not free tier eligible:
Tagging Cost Management advice: Whenever you are creating a cloud resource, tag it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning up Resources You&#39;ve Created</title>
      <link>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 17:39:55 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cloudayolla.github.io/overview/cleanup/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations, you have managed to complete all the labs! This was intensive, but now we need to make sure that we clean-up our cloud account. This should take approximately 5 minutes, and ensures on-going costs are not incurred.
Below is a reminder if you haven&amp;rsquo;t terminated the resources. Perform the steps below, in the order that they are written.
ML Module  Open the Amazon SageMaker service Open the Notebook tab and select your notebook.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>